Where...
Where am I...?
What am I...
It's done.
Are you all right?
Do you feel any pain or discomfort?
Who is he?
I'm glad you came back safe and sound, Re-l.
Re-l?
Is Re-l here too?
Chief.
How are you feeling?
I guess we can let him wake up.
Miss Re-l?
Sure, no problem.
What is this?
What's going on?
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
Re-l.
We're at a loss as to what to do with you.
Your selfish actions were well beyond the bounds of a citizen.
The same can be said of you as well, Raul.
Yes, sir.
However, the benefits accompanying her return are great.
Benefits that may even sustain Romdeau.
The Administrator is happy about that.
Grandfather is?
I didn't know what was going on at first,
but I gradually realized
that for some reason, my - Vincent Law's - consciousness
had entered Re-l.
In other words, I saw everything through Re-l's eyes
and heard everything through Re-l's ears.
meditation   sacred eye of the void
Re-l.
Swan.
I should've known you'd be on time.
Swan?
I told you in the car, didn't I?
Am I making a nuisance of myself?
No, it's just that you weren't wearing your usual lab coat, so...
Sorry.
But my will has no effect.
And I have no influence on Re-l's actions.
The only one who knows I exist within her...
is me.
Good?
Yeah.
I see. That's good.
Indeed.
The chef here is excellent.
It's strange...
Just a short while ago, it was difficult finding enough to eat.
The outside world and Romdeau are completely different.
That is why people call Romdeau a cradle.
And those who would rest within the cradle must be citizens...
citizens like you and me.
My grandfather...
seems to only be happy about what I brought back to Romdeau.
I understand.
I understand that what is important to
Grandfather is finding a way to sustain Romdeau.
I just happened to act according to his wishes.
I understand that.
I know I shouldn't link that thought to what I've lost...
Re-l...
I'm just whining, aren't I.
Sorry.
Time skipped forward again.
No, my consciousness was just
nonexistent during that interval of time.
This world is very fragmented to me.
There is something I desperately want to ask Re-l.
What happened to Pino and me in this city?
Of course, this question doesn't reach her.
The next day,
Re-l started asking to go see the Centzon.
Talk about thorough preparation.
I don't want to allow external pathogens to enter Romdeau.
You're nostalgic, perhaps?
Do you want to see Vincent Law?
I heard my name spoken for the first time that day.
Just as I suspected, I'm somewhere in this city...
No.
But for some reason, Re-l refused to see me.
Unable to exert my will, her world frustrates me.
Is there any way for me to let her know I'm here?
What?
Well, I just felt that you may have changed a bit
from the way you were before.
What makes you say that?
At dinner the other day, you apologized
three times within a short amount of time.
The first time was when you couldn't tell who I was.
The second time was when you talked about the Administrator.
The third time was when you
dropped the dessert spoon on the floor.
It's only natural to apologize when you're at fault, isn't it?
How awful.
It seems Daedalus told you
stories about what a selfish bitch I am.
See?
You were like that last night; you're somewhat self-deprecating.
I didn't hear anything from the Chief.
I did my own research.
On me?
Yes.
I am your mental health counselor, after all.
That's news to me!
I'll take care of you until you can get
back on your feet as a citizen again.
You seem worse than an Entourage.
So, re-indoctrination... to be a model citizen.
My memory is blank for about a week afterwards.
I don't know what happened to Re-l during that time.
I want to show you something, Swan.
What?
I haven't even shown it to Daedalus.
Can you keep a secret?
An autoreiv...
Pino!
Let go! Let go!
This girl...
I hate being in the dark! Let me out of here!
We don't have a choice!
You're infected!
I hate you too, Re-l!
Doing that to Vince!
I'm gonna get out of here to rescue Vince!
Don't be ridiculous!
Do you want to go outside and become scrap metal?
Pino said she'd rescue me.
What has actually happened to me?
Re-l.
Let's go see Vincent tomorrow.
It'll be all right.
I'll be with you.
It's set so that FP rays will be
injected into his body at the slightest move.
This has been explained to him, of course.
Since you shot an FP bullet in front of
him before, the warning was effective.
Vincent...
Are you sure you can come so close?
It's been a while, Re-l Mayer.
It is true that I will die if I make any moves right now.
However...
I can at least kill you before I die.
Then why don't you?
I just find it wasteful to die for the sake of one traitorous bitch.
Why... did you betray me?
Why?
Re-l betrayed me...
I never expected to see myself like this through her eyes.
Are that Vincent Law and this Vincent Law one and the same?
But he has a will that is distinct from mine...
So, who am I?
The "me" within Re-l...
Was it shocking?
I'm all right.
Do you know why I had you see him?
No.
Re-l.
Have you recently felt as though
you periodically lose track of time?
No...
It's just that, in my head...
In your head?
It feels as though... someone's talking to me.
That's Vincent Law.
Hello, Vincent.
You can see me?
I had Re-l see you so that you could see yourself.
To be sure, Re-l was shocked,
but compared to the shock you felt...
So that was why.
Yes.
Thanks to the shock of seeing yourself,
I was able to summon you from within Re-l.
In order to do so, someone
needed to acknowledge your existence...
someone like me.
Why am I in Miss Re-l?
Re-l's consciousness is in withdrawal.
Put more simply, she has multiple personality disorder.
Her guilt, the fact that she betrayed Vincent Law,
has created you as a separate personality.
Wait a minute.
Then I'm...
I'm...
not Vincent Law?
Not in a real sense, no.
But that's...
Have you felt as though you've lost track of time?
Y-Yes.
That's incontrovertible proof that you're not Vincent Law himself.
If your will existed as an independent entity,
you wouldn't let the will of another
person such as Re-l infringe on yours.
Just like she subconsciously created you,
she is subconsciously making your consciousness "skip".
What should I do?
Removing you by force would only destabilize Re-l.
This session ends here.
Let's meet again, Vincent.
Go back to Re-l after I count from ten.
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Wait.
Six...
I still want to talk to you.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
Vincent's inside me?
That idea is in poor taste.
Miss Re-l! Don't touch it!
Hello, Vincent.
It's been a week.
I thought Re-l wouldn't come here anymore.
What?
Do you know Re-l called me?
No...
I recorded the call.
Swan, I'm not coming back to the clinic anymore.
It's true that the matter concerning Vincent is bothering me,
but it's also unpleasant to have such things said to me.
I'd thought we could have an easygoing relationship, but...
It's unfortunate.
But Re-l came.
If Re-l's consciousness is skipping just like yours does...
No, that she came here means that
your will subconsciously asserted itself.
My will did...?
Come out, Re-l.
Why am I here?
Last I remember, I was in my room and...
Swan!
Swan?
Where am I?
Vincent.
It's your doing, isn't it, Vincent.
Mine...?
You're subconsciously trying to take over Re-l.
"Take over"?!
All this time, you've been waiting for a chance, haven't you?
While studying her...
Stop!
Swan, I...
What should I do?
What can I do to disappear from inside Re-l?
You don't mind disappearing?
If it's to save Re-l...
You know how, don't you, Swan?
There is a way.
Show her your past.
My past...
That'd be difficult.
I don't have memories of my past.
That's all right.
You're not Vincent anyway.
It can be a past of your choosing.
A past of my choosing...
Put another way, your desires...
Relax.
You will travel to a world of your desires...
to a world you desire.
And what about that?
Yes, sir. It's all going smoothly.
Having talented subordinates like you makes my job easier.
Thank you, sir.
By the way,
I hear you're quite the loving husband.
Who said that?
It's nothing to be embarrassed about, is it?
As someone who'll soon have a family,
I'd like to ask you what the secret to a happy marriage is.
Are you not enjoying yourself?
We're both so busy.
Oh, is that why you're sulking?
With me as the Security Bureau Chief and
you as an Information Bureau career woman,
it's inevitable that finding time to see each other is difficult.
Besides, once you two get married, you'll be
seeing more of each other than you'd like every day.
Daedalus.
I'm sorry that my sister's so selfish.
You're late.
Sorry, sorry. My classes ran late.
I wonder.
I heard that you don't actually go to school much.
It's boring.
Don't worry though. I'll make sure I attend enough to pass.
I've heard that you're an excellent student, Daedalus.
Only when it comes to test scores.
I've heard a lot about you as well, Chief Vincent.
Do you feel comfortable with the fact that a model
citizen like yourself is marrying my tomboy of a sister-
Daedalus.
Well, I'm only too happy to welcome you as my brother.
I'm happy you'll be my brother as well.
Honestly, he's so cheeky.
But I'm glad he likes me.
I've never come across anyone who doesn't.
Everyone likes you - it's almost annoying.
Jealous?
I never said that.
Oops.
Miss Re-l, don't touch it!
It's been a week,
Re-l.
Why am I... here again?
It's all right, Re-l.
I'm so glad, Re-l!
I was worried because you weren't home.
Did you play hooky from school again, Daedalus?
What are you talking about, Re-l?
Get a hold of yourself.
Vincent Law has escaped!
A cogito-infected companion-type autoreiv broke in and...
He'll probably find you and attack you.
If it comes to that, use this.
Swan, please look after Re-l.
You let him escape, didn't you.
I... don't know.
I told you.
It's subconscious.
Re-l, you loved Vincent.
Of course.
Vincent is my fiancé.
See?
Vincent,
you haphazardly mixed actual memories with your desires.
So Re-l is confused.
She has lost sight of the distinction
between her real past and your desires.
Isn't that right, Re-l?
Vincent's coming to see me!
Wait, Vincent!
What should I do?
Kill Re-l.
You only exist in Re-l's imagination
so that she can escape from the
fact that she betrayed Vincent Law.
So if you kill Re-l in her imagination,
her split identity will become one.
Let us visit the past you desired again...
Vince!
I missed you!
Pino...
Why do you have something like that?
I have to...
kill Re-l.
What?
To save her.
To save Re-l-Re-l?
Yeah...
It's okay to kill Re-l-Re-l, even though we're trying to save her?
This world isn't real, so...
Well, not that you'd know what I'm talking about, but...
Then let's kill Re-l-Re-l.
Hey, Pino...
What are you...
There's no need to ask; I'll kill her.
See?
This isn't real.
Swan.
This is Re-l's imaginary world.
So...
The other you must kill her.
Kill her...
Kill her!
Kill her!!!
You're wrong.
I should've noticed from the start.
I would never let this go, even for Miss Re-l.
The point at which Miss Re-l had the necklace,
made a world like this plainly impossible.
Then... who are you here?
If this world isn't real, who are you?
You're here.
Are you going to reject that existence?
You've lost sense of who you are,
so you'll never find anywhere to belong,
Vincent...
But... it's not here.
I'm not here.
I don't like it.
I can't take this off, no matter what...
Your... necklace.
You're also a PROXY.
I don't like men who smell of other women.
The necklace feels the same way too, I'm sure.
Even so, I want to protect Re-l.
I see.
No, Re-l-Re-l!
Goodbye.
Vincent,
it's my turn.
What's the matter?
Where... are we?
What are you talking about?
It's nothing.
Get a grip.
Romdeau's near.
Romdeau...
You're not the only one who's anxious.
I wonder what's going to happen...
to you and me.
"I think, therefore you are", huh.
Will you give me that necklace before we reach Romdeau?
What?
I just felt like asking.
Get some rest, Vincent.
Good night, Miss Re-l.
Good night, Vincent.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
The man vanished to resist fate.
With enough hatred to incinerate himself,
the bizarre divided soul becomes one.
meditation  the place where time ends